Guide to the Community Service Society Archives
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Charity Organization Society
  - Subseries V.1: Alphabetic Files
    - National Information Bureau 1924-26; 1919-22; 1922-23 See also: Merchants Assn of NY & National Investigation Bureau & Organization of National Information (Box 148)
    - National Investigation Bureau & Organization of National Information (Forerunner of National Information Bureau) See: Merchants Assn. of NY (Box 148)
    - National Social Unit Organization (Historical interest lies in showing the beginnings of organized attempts at community organization based on local community effects) (Box 148)
    - Neighborhood Buildings - 1905 (Proposal by COS of need for neighborhood centers where, in addition to recreational facilities, relief needs could be met) (Box 149)
    - Nels Anderson Study See: Welfare Council - Study - Homeless Cases 1931-32 (Box 149)
    - New York Assn. of Day Nurseries See: Assn. of Day Nurseries (Box 149)
    - NYC Charities Dept. of 1898-1903 (Box 149)
    - New York City Charter Bill (Point of view of COS about the City Charter Bill Provision 1911 has historical interest as reflective of the times) (Box 149)
    - New York City:
      - Commission Work Bureau 1931-32 (Box 149)
      - Conference on Social Work 1914-25 (Box 149)
      - Crime Commission (Box 149)
      - Department of Charities 1915-16 (Predecessor of Dept. of Welfare) (Box 149)
      - Dept, of Hospitals 1899-1908 (Box 149)
      - Dept. of Public Welfare - Reports on the Division & Boards of Child Welfare. (Box 150)
      - Dept, of Recreation - Dept, of Docks (Box 150)
      - Dept. of Welfare See: New York City Dept. of Charities (Box 150)
      - Police Dept. - Relations COS (Box 150)
      - Historical Contents:[indent#2]
        - Mendicancy (Box 150)
        - Police Department and Relief – 1917 (Box 150)
        - Police Work with Delinquent Boys – 1917 (Box 150)
        - Police Welfare Bureau 1917 (Box 150)
        - Appointment of Women as Police Officers (Box 150)
      - Probation System (Box 150)
    - New York Emergency Work Commission Report - Dec, 1931-May 1932 (Box 150)
    - New York House & School Industry - 1910-1919 (Describes COS's arrangement with this organization for training women for household jobs. Interesting example of a primitive form of vocational training) (Box 150)
    - New York School of Social Work:
      - October 1903-February 1904 (Early courses in Philanthropy - Beginnings of what became New York School of Social Work, October 1903-February 1904) (Box 150)
      - 1909-17 (Contains important material e.g. Field work plans of family agencies other than NY COS -- Subjects taught in NYSSCO curriculum -- Assignments of students to COS districts -- Evaluative statements about students -- COS staff teaching at school) (Box 151)
      - 1911-12 Miscellaneous See: 1909 paper on Co-operation Casework (Box 151)
      - 1918-26 (Box 151)
      - Committee on Field Work 1925-1927 (Box 151)
      - 1909-20 COS District Plans for Field Work Training (Box 151)
      - Extension Courses - 1926-28 (Box 151)
      - Field Work 1917-22 (Box 151)
      - Full record of one student’s experience 1912 (Box 151)
      - Miss Mary P. Wheeler's file (Box 151)
      - Carnegie Building (Box 152)
      - Richmond & Lee 1910-17] (Box 152)
    - New York State Conference on Social Work (Box 152)
    - New York State Conference of Charities & Correction (Box 152)
    - Miscellaneous Programs 1900 (First Conference)1936 See Publication Box - Mezzanine Shelves (Box 152)
    - New York State – Probation (Box 152)
    - Nursing Service - COS 1900-1903-1904 (Box 152)
    - Nursing Service - Field Work 1910-12 (Contain s Mary E. Richmond's course for nurses: "Sickness as a Family Problem") (Box 152)
    - Old Age Assistance (Box 152)
    - Orphans (Box 152)
    - Penny Provident Fund (Box 152)
    - Personalities:
      - Bannard, Otto T. (Box 152)
      - Davison, Henry P. (Box 152)
      - Devine, Edward T. (Box 153)
      - DeForest, Robert W. (Box 153)
      - de Schweinits, Karl (Box 153)
      - Famous Autographs:
        - Harry Hopkins (Box 153)
        - Jessie Taft (Box 153)
        - Will Rogers (Box 153)
        - Homer Folks (Box 153)
        - Betty Rogers (Box 153)
        - Robert La Follette (Box 153)
        - Kermit Roosevelt (Box 153)
        - Frances Perkins (Box 153)
        - James Rorty (Box 153)
        - Fiorello H. La Guardia (Box 153)
        - Leonard Wood (Box 153)
        - William Hodson[end#2] (Box 153)
        - Ford, Louise F. (Box 153)
        - Kellog, C.D.-First General Secretary of COS (Box 153)
        - La Guardia, Fiorello (Box 153)
        - Hodson, William (Box 153)
        - Kelley, Florence (Contain s letters from Jane Adams and Julia C. Lathrop) (Box 153)
        - Kellog, Arthur P. (Box 153)
        - Kennedy, John S. (Box 153)
        - Lee, Porter R. (Box 153)
        - Purdy, Lawson (Box 153)
        - Richmond, Mary E.: (Box 154)
          - (1) 1893-1915 (Box 154)
          - (2) 1916-1930 (Box 154)
          - (3) The Work of District Secretary See also: Richmond, Mary E.[end#2] (Box 154)
      - Sutro, Lionel - 1916 (Box 154)
      - Tousley, Clare M, (Reprints of articles by CMT re interpretation of casework services) (Box 154)
    - Wald, Lillian D. (Box 154)
    - Personnel Philanthropy - School of See: New York School of Social Work (Box 154)
    - Politics in Charities - 1902 (An interesting example of social action to improve State Hospital Care) (Box 154)
    - Position Classification (not found, 10/1979) See also: Casework - Visitors Qualifications (Box 155)
    - Press & Social Work See also: Charities Dispute 1916 (Box 155)
    - Press & Social Work - 1907-11 (Box 155)
    - Press & Social Work - 1912-14 (Contains newspaper articles attacking charity - critical correspondence and replies) (Box 155)
    - Press & Social Work - 1915-16 (Box 155)
    - Press & Social Work - 1916-1924 (Box 155)
    - Press and Social Work. Criticisms of COS:
      - Various newspaper clippings -February 1897 -December 1898 (Box 155)
      - Various newspaper clippings - January 1899 (Box 155)
      - Various newspaper clippings - 1906, 1907, 1908 (Box 155)
      - Various newspaper clippings – 1911 (Box 155)
      - Press and Social Work (Box 155)
    - Press and Social Work -Evening Graphic (Box 155)
    - Press and Social Work -Harpers Weekly:
      - October 1914-December 1914 (Box 155)
      - September 1914 (Box 155)
      - August 1914 (Box 156)
    - Press and Social Work - Lawsuit 1888 - DeCosta - Howell (Suit brought against COS and Charles D. Kellogg for alleged libel) (Box 156)
    - Press and Social Work -Miscellaneous Items (Box 156)
    - Press and Social Work -NY American Attack on COS (Box 156)
    - Press and Social Work -New York Evening Post 1915-1920 (Shows close relationship and good publicity given to COS Shows Post's fund-raising for relief of elderly couples) (Box 156)
    - The Press and Social Work -Pearson's Magazine (Pearson's Magazine articles by George Creel) (Box 156)
    - Professional Education: (Box 156)
    - 1900 Syllabus "The Care of the Poor" (Box 156)
    - 1900 Lecture on "The New Concepts of Charity" (Box 156)
    - 1929-30 Committee on Preparation for Social Work -Limited data (Box 156)
    - Professional Education See: Casework - Teaching Conference 1921 –Klein; See: Casework –Training (Box 156)
    - Program: Community Development in the Depression (Box 156)
    - Prostitution See: Committee of Fourteen 1911-1926 (Box 157)
    - Protestant Fund -1933-1936 (COS statistics on numbers of Protestants served and costs; developed during the "Blaine Committee" fund raising era. Important for a study of Protestant agencies, volume of work with Protestants, etc. Contains pros & cons re a Protestant Federation and centralized fund-raising) (Box 157)
    - Provident Loan Society (Box 157)
    - Public Outdoor Relief (Box 157)
    - Publicity (Box 157)
    - Queens Family Service -Survey of Queens (Box 157)
    - Queen s Family Service (includes also Citizens Committee - limited data) (Box 157)
    - Radio Skits (Box 157)
    - Records Retention (Box 157)
    - Red Cross (Box 157)
    - Registration Bureau (Box 157)
    - Registration Bureau, 1892-1936 (Box 157)
    - Relief See Also: Districts - Relief Budget (Box 158)
    - Relief - Harlem - Mt. Morris District 1931-32 (Box 158)
    - Records - Retention Schedule Plan (Box 158)
    - Relief - Strikers Families - COS position 1916 (Box 158)
    - Relief Giving - Conference on (Box 158)
    - Hartsdale Conference - April 1927 (Box 158)
    - Relief Supplementation - Fitzherbert Study (Box 158)
    - Relief Work - Suggestions 1906-1909 (Very important for study of emerging casework processes, ) Contain s instructions to districts re: Relief giving and management Contains notes on a class given in Boston on investigation. Contains articles on particular groups, e.g. working mothers who might be in need of relief) (Box 158)
    - Reports to Central Council (not found, 10/1979):
      - 11/15/16 - 12/5/17 (Box 158)
      - 1/4/18 - 5/9/28 (Box 158)
      - Research(not found, 10/1979) See also: Casework - (Research Plans (Technical Planning Committee) (Box 158)
      - Richmond, Mary E.[indent] (Box 158)
      - See: American Association of Societies for Organizing Family (Box 158)
      - Social Work (Box 158)
      - See: National Alien Relief Committee (Box 158)
      - See: Casework - Treatment (Box 158)
      - See: Personalities - Mary S Richmond (Box 158)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 158)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 158)
    - Grants to COS (Box 159)
    - Mrs. Sage's gifts (Folder also contains Memorial on death of Mrs. Sage, together with news clipping) (Box 159)
    - Russell Sage Foundation - Winter Exchange (Box 159)
    - Sabbatical Leaves:
      - Inquires into practice – 1926 (Box 159)
      - For discussion, refer to minutes of D.S. meeting (Box 159)
    - Saint Louis Exposition See: Exhibit s - World's Fair 1903 (Box 159)
    - Salary Scale Study 1923-25 (also 191? & 1918) (not found, 10/1979):
      - Comparative scales as reported by agencies (Box 159)
      - Early attempt to evolve position classification (Box 159)
      - See: American Association for Organizing Family Social Work (Box 159)
    - Saloons - Investigation of 1914-16 (Important study in a study of care of homeless men (men slept overnight in saloons) (Box 159)
    - Sanders, Catherine See: Studies - Sanders - Child Placing (Box 159)
    - Scannell, Ruth - March 1938 See: Studies - History of COS 1882-1935 (Box 159)
    - School Census (Box 159)
    - School Lunches See: Home Economics - School Lunches (Box 159)
    - Self Support Loan Fund 1907-11 (Box 159)
    - Self Support Loan Fund 1914-17 (Box 159)
    - Seminar s - Fitch - Industry & Social Work (Box l60)
    - "Six Characters in Search of "___________" Kasius - 1925 (Prepared in connection with Mobilization for Human Needs Conference - Washington, D.C. - September 1925) (Box l60)
    - Smith, Zilpha D See: Casework - Friendly Visitors Course (Box l60)
    - Social Action See also: Politics in Charities (Box l60)
    - Social Conditions - Department for improving 1907-1924 (Organization of Dept. for improving Social Conditions Meeting of Central Council to consider question of new department and discussion of appointing Lawrence Veiller (Box l60)
    - Socia l Laws Handbook - 1915-1917 (Box 16l)
    - Social Security & Social Case Work - Paper by Russell H. Kurtz - 1938 (Box 16l)
    - Social Service Exchange - 1912-1933 (Box 16l)
    - Steps leading to transfer of SSE from COS to Welfare Council (Box 16l)
    - Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children (Box 16l)
    - Staff Lists (Box 16l)
    - Staff Paper - "Column Write" (Contains many items covering agency activities - its personnel, etc, which could be valuable aid to an historical researcher) (Box 16l)
    - Staff Turnover Study See: America n Association for Organizing Family Social Work -1927-30 (Box 16l)
    - State Board of Charities (Box 16l)
    - State Charities Aid Association (Box 162)
    - Studies:
      - Two hundred families in COS district – 1911 (Box 162)
      - Italian Families – Gramercy (Box 162)
      - Intake - Gramercy District (Box 162)
      - Housing in Chelsea-Lowell District – 1935 (Box 162)
      - Food Orders - 1915 - Emma Winslow (a study of 500 food orders sent to families in need) (Box 162)
      - Court Hearing Procedure - Alice D. Taggart (Box 162)
      - COS Program in Depression Years (Box 162)
      - Child Care Agencies - Ethel Taylor (Box 162)
      - Intake - Case Material - 1928 (Box 162)
      - Joint Committee on Home - 1916 (Mary Hurebutts' study of homes - comments by COS in its' cases which were included shows the work of the time) (Box 162)
      - Child Placing - Sanders (Good picture of child placement needs in NYC as of 1923 as seen by COS - Catherine Sanders, author. (Box 163)
      - Child Placing - Taylor 1929 (Box 163)
      - Crime & Behavior - Van Kleeck – 1930 (Mary Van Kleeck's Study for Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement Contains a statement as to causes for crime & criminal behavior) (Box 163)
      - Foster Care (Box 163)
      - Food Orders - 1915 - Emma Winslow (A study of 500 food orders sent to families in need) (Box 163)
      - History of COS, 1882-1935 (Ruth Scannell, March 1938) See Box 128. (Box 163)
      - Old Age - Ethel Taylor, 1929 (Box 163)
      - Relief, 1928 - Grace Marcus:[indent#2] (Box 163)
      - Draft of Grace Marcus' book (Box 163)
      - Miss Marcus' summarized report (Box 163)
      - Responses of social workers to report (Box 163)
      - Russell Sage Foundation Study, 1926 - Comparative Statistics for 39 Family Welfare Agencies on relief practices (Box 163)
      - Material from American Association for Organizing Family Social Work bearing on their proposed relief study[end #2] (Box 163)
      - Relief - COS 1921 – 1927 (Box 163)
      - Supervision - Questionnaire on Methods - Joanna C. Colcord, 1916 (Box 163)
      - Venereal Disease - Grace Child (Box 163)
      - Casework (Box l64)
      - Manhattanville (Stauffer) (Box l64)
      - Puerto Ricans (Box l64)
    - Survey Associates (Box l64)
    - Taylor, Ethel. See: Studies - Child Placing, 1929 & Studies - Old Age (Box l64)
    - Tax Exemption (Box l64)
    - Tenement House Committee:
      - Correspondence, 1898-1912 (Box l64)
      - Correspondence, 1918-1937 (Box 165)
      - General (Box 165)
      - Annual Reports (Box 165)
      - Adequacy of Courts in New York, Tenement Committee 1917 (Box 165)
      - Architects' Drawings, 1914 (Box 165)
      - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1914 (Box 165)
      - Cellar-Basement Dwellings, 1917 (Box 165)
      - Cement Blocks, 1915 (Box 165)
      - Clean-up Week (Box 165)
      - Committee - Interior Planning of Tenement Houses, 1914 (Box 165)
      - Committee of Fourteen, 1917-1922 (Box 165)
      - Complaints, 1914 (Box 166)
      - Complaints - Action Taken, 1914 (Box 166)
      - Concrete Houses (Box 166)
      - Exhibit, 1899-1900 (Clayton and McNeary Bills) (Box 166)
      - Fire Prevention (Box 166)
      - Fireproofing Old Law Tenements Committee, 1922 (Box 166)
      - Five Steps Forward (Box 166)
      - Four Family House - Dowling Bill, 1918 (Box 166)
      - For You (Box 166)
      - Heights of Buildings, 1912-1915 (Box 166)
      - Housing Shortage, 1918 (Box 166)
      - Improving Housing (Box 166)
      - Inspection Legislation, 1911 (Box 166)
      - Legislation, 1914, 1917, 1918, 1921 Black Bill (Box 167)
      - Legislation:
        - Dodge and Leninger Bills (Box 167)
        - Lawson Bill (revision of) I (Box 167)
        - Lawson Bill (revision of) II (Box 167)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1914, 1917, 1918, 1919-1922 (Box 167)
      - Model Tenement, 1914-1917 (Box 167)
      - Model Tenement Districts, 1917 (Box 167)
      - "Murder" Stable Block, 1917 (Box 168)
      - National Housing Association, 1914-1917 (Box 168)
      - Neighborhood Association, 1914 (Box 168)
      - New York City Bureau of Buildings, 1914 (Box 168)
      - New York City - Consolidation of City Departments, 1914 (Box 168)
      - New York City Tenement House Department, 1914 (Box 168)
      - New York City Tenement House Department, 1921 (Box 168)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Box 168)
      - Open Stairs, 1922 (Box 168)
      - Photographs, 1917 (not found, 10/1979) (Box 168)
      - Prosecutions - Decisions (violation of THC laws), 1914 (Box 168)
      - Prostitution, 19l4 (Box 168)
      - Publications - "For You" 1914-1917 (Box 168)
      - Publications - "For You" 1917 (Box 168)
      - Publications - Small House Report - Newdick (Box 168)
      - Publicity (Box 169)
      - Rats, Children and Houses (Box 169)
      - Reports, 1917 (Box 169)
      - Reports, 1918 (Box 169)
      - The Residential Districts (protecting) 1915 (Box 169)
      - Rooms or Cells Sanitary Code, 19l4 (Box 169)
      - Shall the Law Permit.. ., 1913 (Box 169)
      - Taxation - Single Tax - tax exemption on new buildings (Box 169)
      - Tenants League - responsibility, etc. (Box 169)
      - Tenement Construction (Box 169)
      - Testimonials (Box 169)
      - Three Family House Campaign, 1912-1915 (Box 169)
      - Three Family Houses: (Box 170)
        - 1913-1914 (Box 170)
        - 1914, (2 Folders) (Box 170)
        - 1918 (Box 170)
        - Advisory Council of Real Estate Interests, 1915 (Box 170)
        - Cotillo Bill, 1915 (Box 170)
        - Lawson Bill, 1917 (Box 170)
        - Newspaper Clippings, 1917 (Box 170)
        - Drawings, Plans (Box 170)
        - Three Family Houses, 1914-1917, 1915-1926 (Box 171)
      - Thomas, Andrew - Architect (Box 171)
      - War Housing, 1918 (Box 171)
      - What the Law Requires (Box 171)
      - Why Abandoned Buildings Should be Demolished (Box 171)
      - Wire Fences, 1915 (Box 171)
      - Wire Fences, 1917 (Box 171)
      - Zoning, 1917 (Box 171)
      - Minutes, 1898-1917 (l volume) (Box 171)
      - Minutes, 1908-1937 (four Folders) (Box 172)
      - Correspondence, 1900-1901 (l volume) (Box 172)
      - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 173)
      - Reports and miscellaneous (Box 173)
      - Reports and miscellaneous (Box 174)
      - Hearings Clippings (Box 175)
      - Clippings (Box 176-179)
    - Thanksgiving Dinners, 1910-1921 (Examples of "in kind" giving which may be pertinent to future "social progress report.") (Box 180)
    - Theatre Investigation, 1906-1912 (Contents show COS representation on a committee to investigate movies, places of entertainment, dance halls, etc. Result: Draft of a bill to regulate places of amusement. Reflect s concern in 1904- about violence in movies, possible destruction, effects on young people, etc.) (Box 180)
    - Testimonials, 1887-1895 (not found, 10/1979) (Box 180)
    - Training. See Casework – training; Casework - Visitors in Training (COS training course outline) (Box 180)
    - Transients, 1935 (See Also: Welfare Council - care of unattached) (Box 180)
    - Transportation Agreement. See Charity Rates, 1923 (Box 180)
    - Tuberculosis (Contains Study, 1902 by Miss M. E. Very, consisting of interviews with NYC physicians on cases and prevention of TB (See leather book.) (Box 180)
    - Tuberculosis: Report on TB Congress in Berlin, May 1899 (Box 180)
    - Tuberculosis: Report on cases under care of Committee on Prevention of Tuberculosis (AICP, 1902-1903) (Box 180)
    - Tuberculosis, 1916-1917 (Contains intensive study of four tubercular families, 1916 Forcible removal of tubercular individuals from families) (Box 180)
    - Unemployment, 1904-1915, (2 Folders) (Box 181)
    - Unemployment in New York City - Welfare Council reports (Box 181)
    - Unemployment relief, Governor's Committee on, 1935 (Box 181)
    - United Charities Store (proposal for joint purchases and supply) United States Children's Bureau. See: Bureau in the Interest of Children Children's Bureau, United States (Box 181)
    - Vacation School Proposal, 1894 (Box 182)
    - Vacation Services See: Fresh Air Fund; See: Fresh Air Home (Box 182)
    - Vagrancy (Box 182)
    - Veiller, Lawrence See: Social Conditions - Dept. for Improving (Box 182)
    - Venereal Disease See: Studies Venereal Disease - Grace Child; See: Committee on Venereal Disease (Box 182)
    - Visitors-Friendly (Box 182)
    - Visitors' Handbook (Box 182)
    - Visitors-Organization (Box 182)
    - Vocational Service for Juniors - Co-Op Plan COS (Case Summaries suggest range of services in behalf of children being given by district caseworkers) (Box 182)
    - Volunteers (Box 182)
    - Volunteers: (Box 183)
      - Association of (Box 183)
      - General (Box 183)
      - Lenten Classes 1915-1917 (Box 183)
      - Meeting of March 1917 (Box 183)
      - Monthly Reports 1924-1925 (Box 183)
      - Monthly Reports 1927 (Box 183)
      - Statistics (Box 183)
      - Study Class 1911-1916 (Box 183)
      - Training of 1917-1819 (Criteria employed in judging work, types of assignments, school courses given) (Box 183)
    - Wartime Activities See: Aliens Interned - 1918 (Box 183)
    - Wayfarer's Lodge (Started by COS in 1893 as Woodyard, See: Woodyard 1893-1919 (Box 184)
    - Welfare Council:
      - 1927 (Mr. William Matthews of A.I.C.P. active Beginnings of community interest in problems of aged) (Box 184)
      - Beginnings (Box 184)
      - Central Registration Bureau - 1933-1934 (Box 184)
      - Chronically 111 Study - 1931 (Box 184)
      - Coordinating Committee on Unemployment, 1930-1931 (Box 184)
      - Coordinating Committee on Unemployment 1934-1935 (Box 185)
      - Housekeeping Service Report 1938-1943 (Box 185)
      - Study - Homeless Cases:
        - Logan Thomas Studies (Confidential Report on the Greater New York Gospel Mission Report on the Homeless Hen's Department of the Jewish Social Service Association) (Box 185)
        - Nels Anderson Study (Confidential Report on the Hebrew Sheltering and Immigrant Aid Society of America) (Box 185)
    - Study Homeless Cases - 1926 (14 Agencies) (Box 185)
    - Welfare Council - Study-Homeless Cases – 1931 (Box 186)
      - Nels. Anderson (Study Report on the Men's Social Service Dept. of the Salvation Army in New York City) (Box 186)
    - Welfare Council - Study - Homeless Cases 1932
      - Nels Anderson (Box 186)
      - The Method and Terminology of the Psychiatrists (Box 186)
      - Municipal Lodging House of New York City (Part I-II) (Box 186)
    - Welfare Council Bulletin (Contains only the following issues:
      - January 1930 (Box 186)
      - February & March 1930 (Box 186)
      - January 1931 (Box 186)
      - March 1931 (Box 186)
      - April 1931 (Box 186)
      - June 1931 (Box 186)
    - Welfare Council Committee - Aged - 1927-1931
      - Material on needs, suggested solutions & reactions to legislative proposals re aged, from minutes of Welfare Council Committee on aged. (Box 186)
      - Establishment of Central Bureau on Care of Aged - 1927 at Welfare Council (Box 186)
      - COS policy re Care of Aged - 1929 (Box 186)
    - Widowed Mothers - State Committee on Relief of 1913-1914 (Box 187)
    - Widow's Pension:
      - April 1899 - March 1912 (Box 187)
      - 1912-1914 (Box 187)
      - 1907-1919 (Box 187)
      - December 1910-November 1917 (Box 188)
      - May 1912-March 1913 (Box 188)
      - 1913 - Abstract (Box 188)
      - 1913-1914 (Box 188)
      - February 1913-October 1920 (Box 189)
      - Mr. Pearson's file - Cases and Reports (Box 189)
    - Winslow, Emma A. See: Home Economics & Social Work Training Course (Box 189)
    - Woodyard See also: Bread Line (Box 189)
    - Woodyard - 1893-1910 (Box 189)